Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 11. Water and mineral resources files
  - Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 298)
  - Water & Power, Accession no. M0365 (Box 299)
  - Water & Power - Colorado River Basin, Accession no. M0365 (Box 300)
  - Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 371)
- Unprocessed Additions
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 001 (Box 301)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 002 (Box 302)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 003 (Box 303)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 004 (Box 304)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 005 (Box 305)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 006 (Box 306)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 007 (Box 307)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 008 (Box 308)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 009 (Box 309)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 010 (Box 310)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 011 (Box 311)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 012 (Box 312)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 013 (Box 313)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 014 (Box 314)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 0115 (Box 315)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 016 (Box 316)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 0117 (Box 317)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 018 (Box 318)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 019 (Box 319)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 020 (Box 320)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 021 (Box 321)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 022 (Box 322)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 023 (Box 323)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 024 (Box 324)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 025 (Box 325)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 026 (Box 326)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 027 (Box 327)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 028 (Box 328)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 029 (Box 329)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 030 (Box 330)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 031 (Box 331)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 032 (Box 332)
  - Unprocessed material, Accession no. 1983-026m; 1983-026m 033 (Box 333)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 001 (Box 334)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 002 (Box 335)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 003 (Box 336)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 004 (Box 337)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 005 (Box 338)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 006 (Box 339)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 007 (Box 340)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 008 (Box 341)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 009 (Box 342)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 010 (Box 343)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 011 (Box 344)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 012 (Box 345)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 013 (Box 346)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 014 (Box 347)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 015 (Box 348)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 016 (Box 349)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 017 (Box 350)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 018 (Box 351)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 019 (Box 352)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 020 (Box 353)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 021 (Box 354)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 022 (Box 355)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m 023 (Box 356)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H10a (Box 357)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H10b (Box 358)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H10c (Box 359)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H11a (Box 360)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H11b (Box 361)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m H11c (Box 362)
  - (Box 363)
  - (Box 364)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-21 (Box 365)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-22 (Box 366)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-23 (Box 367)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-24 (Box 368)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-25 (Box 369)
  - Accession no. 1984-017m, 1984-017m S-26 (Box 370)